<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LAMP Stack</title>
    <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/</link>
    <description>Recent content on LAMP Stack</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://202.56.164.148:5001/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> IoT Application Testing - Complexities &amp; Challenges</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/io-t-application-testing-complexities-and-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/io-t-application-testing-complexities-and-challenges/</guid>
      <description>IoT Application Testing - Complexities &amp;amp; Challenges By Jason Adam Katzenstein Published on May 27, 2022   The Internet of Things (IoT) is a network of physical objects (devices, vehicles, buildings, etc.) embedded with electronics, software, sensors &amp;amp; network connectivity that are designed to collect &amp;amp; exchange data. Enterprises are adopting the IoT for the benefits offered, e.g., operations optimization, cost reduction &amp;amp; improved efficiency.
IoT development &amp;amp; adoption are driven by multiple factors, including readily available low-cost sensors, increased bandwidth &amp;amp; processing power, wide-spread usage of smartphones, availability of big data analysis tools &amp;amp; scalability of IPV6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Reasons for React Native App Development Popularity</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/12-reasons-for-react-native-app-development-popularity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/12-reasons-for-react-native-app-development-popularity/</guid>
      <description>12 Reasons for React Native App Development Popularity By Kerry Elson Published on May 27, 2022   Technology is advancing at a compelling pace. The mobile app market has witnessed explosive growth. In 2018, mobile app downloads accounted for 30 and 77 billion respectively for the App Store and Google Play. Currently, it accounts for 38 and 102 billion. By 2024, it is expected to hit 45 and 139 billion!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Popular eLearning Content Types</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/5-popular-e-learning-content-types/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/5-popular-e-learning-content-types/</guid>
      <description>5 Popular eLearning Content Types By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   You’ve been assigned to create your first training course, and the deadline is approaching quickly. So, what’s next? That’s a bit abrupt beginning sentence for an article, but that’s how it can seem when you get your first e learning content production project. Where do you begin? What kind of final output is needed?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Effective Ways to Improve User Experience on Mobile App</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/7-effective-ways-to-improve-user-experience-on-mobile-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/7-effective-ways-to-improve-user-experience-on-mobile-app/</guid>
      <description>7 Effective Ways to Improve User Experience on Mobile App By Kerry Elson Published on May 27, 2022   Mobile app development starts and finishes with the user. The contrast between a fruitful mobile app and one that falls flat in the market is a quality UX (user experience app design).
Without an intensive comprehension of your target users&amp;rsquo; in-app personal conduct standards or mental underpinnings, you will not have the option to build a mobile product to fulfill a focal objective or surpass customer expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Strong Reasons to Invest in the .NET Framework in 2021</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/7-strong-reasons-to-invest-in-the-net-framework-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/7-strong-reasons-to-invest-in-the-net-framework-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>7 Strong Reasons to Invest in the .NET Framework in 2021 By Ali Fitzgerald Published on May 27, 2022   You may have a great web application idea in mind to solve the pain points of your target audience. However, when it comes to executing that idea, it’s considered wise to bank upon software architects, tech consultants, or seasoned developers. The reason being is they are not only well-versed with the popular tools, technologies, and frameworks that can bring your idea to life in a quick turnaround time but also know the strengths and weaknesses for each viable option available in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 most important questions to ask before Implementing of a chatbot</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/8-most-important-questions-to-ask-before-implementing-of-a-chatbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/8-most-important-questions-to-ask-before-implementing-of-a-chatbot/</guid>
      <description>8 most important questions to ask before Implementing of a chatbot By Kerry Elson Published on May 27, 2022   As companies become more and more dependent on their customers, so the art of customer service and experience becomes increasingly vital.
And, as with all aspects of marketing, the development of innovative and cutting-edge technologies can see a boost in overall sales and engagement.
However, when it comes to the creation of new technology — especially something as bold and boundary-pushing as a chatbot — it’s hard to know where to start or even who to ask.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Tips to Motivate Your Lazy Self</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/8-tips-to-motivate-your-lazy-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/8-tips-to-motivate-your-lazy-self/</guid>
      <description>8 Tips to Motivate Your Lazy Self By Helen G. Williams Published on May 27, 2022   There are going to be days you don’t feel like doing much of anything. The occasional lazy day is fine, but when they become a regular occurrence, within you, something needs to change. People obtain success and meet their goals through motivating or inspiring themselves to take action each day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Class Act: How to Help Yourself Look Sophisticated</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/a-class-act-how-to-help-yourself-look-sophisticated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/a-class-act-how-to-help-yourself-look-sophisticated/</guid>
      <description>A Class Act: How to Help Yourself Look Sophisticated By Joseph Ballard Published on May 27, 2022   As summer comes to a close, it’s time to pack away the flip-flops and shorts, and pull out those expensive, polished shoes for an autumn of accomplishments.
But you don’t have to stop there. Dressing well is just the starting point. The following tips will help you to appear truly sophisticated all season long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A deadly Combination of Pharmaceutical Drugs and Alcohol</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/a-deadly-combination-of-pharmaceutical-drugs-and-alcohol/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/a-deadly-combination-of-pharmaceutical-drugs-and-alcohol/</guid>
      <description>A deadly Combination of Pharmaceutical Drugs and Alcohol By Joseph Ballard Published on May 27, 2022   Many-a-times people who are addicted to alcohol have the tendency to take their medications with alcohol which can at times backfire them instantly as mixing alcohol and medication together can form a very deadly combination which can be extremely dangerous to consume and can also lead towards the stream leading to the edge of death or overdose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Fired Illegally: Get You Right Back with Wrongful Termination Lawyers</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/are-you-fired-illegally-get-you-right-back-with-wrongful-termination-lawyers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/are-you-fired-illegally-get-you-right-back-with-wrongful-termination-lawyers/</guid>
      <description>Are You Fired Illegally: Get You Right Back with Wrongful Termination Lawyers By Joseph Ballard Published on May 27, 2022   Losing a job is more than shocking for one who experiences it. As employment in almost all states in the US is ‘at will’ - means your employer can fire you at any time without explaining any reason, wrongful termination is widespread.
However, despite the ‘ at will’ term of the job, the federal employment law still has declared that it’s illegal if an employer is laid-off by an employee for discriminatory, retaliatory reasons or by violating the job contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Badminton Tips – 7 Tips to Become a Better Badminton Player</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/badminton-tips-7-tips-to-become-a-better-badminton-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/badminton-tips-7-tips-to-become-a-better-badminton-player/</guid>
      <description>Badminton Tips – 7 Tips to Become a Better Badminton Player By Liam Cunningham Published on May 27, 2022   Badminton, like any game, has a lot of subtleties that are not agreeable to beginner players aside from the off chance that they are unveiled to them. However, these subtleties can gigantically influence your chances to win matches and, by and large, to play better badminton.
This article will give you nine clues that you most likely will not have found out about beforehand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Tips for Shooting Photographs in Natural Light</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/basic-tips-for-shooting-photographs-in-natural-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/basic-tips-for-shooting-photographs-in-natural-light/</guid>
      <description>Basic Tips for Shooting Photographs in Natural Light By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   Most people just starting out in photography probably won’t have access to expensive cameras and lighting equipment. But in fact, in terms of creativity, some of the most emotive and affecting images can be captured using natural or available light. There are, however, certain basic tips and tricks that you can use to maximise the effects of natural light and make your work more professional from the get-go, depending on how you want the finished image to look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best 5 Android Frameworks for App Development</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/best-5-android-frameworks-for-app-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/best-5-android-frameworks-for-app-development/</guid>
      <description>Best 5 Android Frameworks for App Development By Jason Adam Katzenstein Published on May 27, 2022   Are you looking for the Best Android Framework that you can consider for app development in 2021? You’re at the right place!
You must have noticed. When a device converts your life from ‘just working’ to making life easier, Android is the reason.
Undoubtedly, Android is the most popular mobile operating system that is open to everyone: developers, designers, engineers, and device manufacturers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billabong Men’s Shorts: A Brief History Of Australia’s Most Iconic Surf Brand</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/billabong-men-s-shorts-a-brief-history-of-australia-s-most-iconic-surf-brand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/billabong-men-s-shorts-a-brief-history-of-australia-s-most-iconic-surf-brand/</guid>
      <description>Billabong Men’s Shorts: A Brief History Of Australia’s Most Iconic Surf Brand By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   Founded in 1973, Billabong has since been one of the leading companies in manufacturing and selling surfing wear. With the company now on its 48th year of operations, let us take a brief look into the history of Australia’s most iconic surf brand.
Before Billabong Gordon Merchant, one of the founders, liked to travel a lot in Australia during the late 60s and 70s, totally embracing the surfing lifestyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brazil Invest in New Transport Monitoring System</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/brazil-invest-in-new-transport-monitoring-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/brazil-invest-in-new-transport-monitoring-system/</guid>
      <description>Brazil Invest in New Transport Monitoring System By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   In a country as rapidly-developing as Brazil it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that the infrastructure is just as quickly expanding. Communications of all kinds get more and more important and more and more busy too, including the physical means of getting from one place to another, especially the land-based means. Many would argue, as the Brazilians do that all this requires some sort of overall co-ordination and monitoring if it is to be kept in at least minimal balance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy Genuine Premier League Football Tickets At Competitive Rates</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/buy-genuine-premier-league-football-tickets-at-competitive-rates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/buy-genuine-premier-league-football-tickets-at-competitive-rates/</guid>
      <description>Buy Genuine Premier League Football Tickets At Competitive Rates By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   Football is undoubtedly one of the most admired and watched sports across the world. Only a handful number of people are there who have never watched any football tournament even once. Premier League, rather English Premier League, is a major and highly significant football tournament that football lovers all over the world love to watch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cannabis In Sports</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/cannabis-in-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/cannabis-in-sports/</guid>
      <description>Cannabis In Sports By Amy Burns Published on May 27, 2022   Now that Canada and many US states have legalized cannabis, dozens of our professional sports teams now live in jurisdictions where recreational cannabis use is legal. Some would argue that since cannabis can make it difficult to focus and reduce coordination, it would hinder athletes’ performance rather than enhance it. However, not every cannabis user experiences those effects to the same degree, and cannabis can also reduce anxiety, which can be useful in high-pressure environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Childhood Care And Early Education</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/childhood-care-and-early-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/childhood-care-and-early-education/</guid>
      <description>Childhood Care And Early Education By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   Early childhood is the time of child brain development. At this time parents have to give focus on child care and early education because at this time child develop their minds and acquire learning and reading skills. These skills help in deciding the great future of children. So parents have to give due care to child development and early childhood education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crypto scams - what are your legal defense and guide to avoid being scammed?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/crypto-scams-what-are-your-legal-defense-and-guide-to-avoid-being-scammed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/crypto-scams-what-are-your-legal-defense-and-guide-to-avoid-being-scammed/</guid>
      <description>Crypto scams - what are your legal defense and guide to avoid being scammed? By Joseph Ballard Published on May 27, 2022   Even the people who do not understand the crypto fad are well-versed in &amp;lsquo;Bitcoin&amp;rsquo; and its decade long bull run in valuation. The rise of &amp;lsquo;Bitcoin&amp;rsquo; has been so significant that the term has become synonymous with the term &amp;lsquo;Crypto&amp;rsquo;.
A cryptocurrency can be understood as a digital currency that can be used to buy goods and services functioning on blockchain technology and online ledger record.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning Chip report shares industry analysis with trends – 2027</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/deep-learning-chip-report-shares-industry-analysis-with-trends-2027/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/deep-learning-chip-report-shares-industry-analysis-with-trends-2027/</guid>
      <description>Deep Learning Chip report shares industry analysis with trends – 2027 By Joseph Ballard Published on May 27, 2022   The report offers an extensive analysis of key growth strategies, drivers, opportunities, key segment, Porter’s Five Forces analysis, and competitive landscape. This study is a helpful source of information for market players, investors, VPs, stakeholders, and new entrants to gain thorough understanding of the industry and determine steps to be taken to gain competitive advantage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Difference between Data science, Artificial intelligence, and Machine learning?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/difference-between-data-science-artificial-intelligence-and-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/difference-between-data-science-artificial-intelligence-and-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Difference between Data science, Artificial intelligence, and Machine learning? By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   Data Science, Machine learning, and Artificial Intelligence (AI) are all part of the same area and are related, they each have their own applications and meanings. There may be some overlaps in these sectors from time to time, but each of these three components has its own set of applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Florida Arrest Records Public Search</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/discovering-florida-arrest-records-public-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/discovering-florida-arrest-records-public-search/</guid>
      <description>Discovering Florida Arrest Records Public Search By Joseph Ballard Published on May 27, 2022   Conducting background checks has become a common practice by various employers nowadays. Basically, it is done either to thoroughly select new employees or assess current workers. With regard to this, one of the most significant information to depend on is Florida Arrest Records. In general, it contains essential facts about a certain individual, keeping you feel more secured and safe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down Payment: The Smart Way to Buy a Car with Bad Credit</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/down-payment-the-smart-way-to-buy-a-car-with-bad-credit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/down-payment-the-smart-way-to-buy-a-car-with-bad-credit/</guid>
      <description>Down Payment: The Smart Way to Buy a Car with Bad Credit By Joseph Ballard Published on May 27, 2022   There are several ways to buy a car, especially with a down payment. If your credit score is low and you have no time to rebuild it, you can put money down to purchase your dream car. It does not matter if you buy a used car or a new one, down payment can improve your bad credit auto loan approval chances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/topic/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/topic/education/</guid>
      <description>Education The process of facilitating learning, or the acquisition of knowledge, morals, and personal development.    PowerPoint Free Course - Tips and Tricks for Business Presentations  Helen G. Williams • May 27, 2022   5 Popular eLearning Content Types  James Anthony Knight • May 27, 2022   How to Teach Yourself a Second Language  Helen G. Williams • May 27, 2022   The Advantages of Using Free Online Courses  Helen G.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eight ways to enhance your knowledge of vocabulary to sound smarter</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/eight-ways-to-enhance-your-knowledge-of-vocabulary-to-sound-smarter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/eight-ways-to-enhance-your-knowledge-of-vocabulary-to-sound-smarter/</guid>
      <description>Eight ways to enhance your knowledge of vocabulary to sound smarter By Helen G. Williams Published on May 27, 2022   English is a language that is full of synonyms, homophones homonyms that seem to make it especially difficult to learn. Enhancing your English language skills is something that you will undoubtedly develop in your career in your lifetime. There are many proven advantages in enhancing your knowledge of vocabulary, but most people have not spent much time learning new vocabulary since from their childhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enforcement of UAE Court’s Judgement in UK</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/enforcement-of-uae-court-s-judgement-in-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/enforcement-of-uae-court-s-judgement-in-uk/</guid>
      <description>Enforcement of UAE Court’s Judgement in UK By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   Civil Lawyers of Dubai upon witnessing such noteworthy change in legal procedures in both countries wish to enlighten our readers to ascertain the point of view adapted by English courts whilst enforcing the judgment of UAE court.
What is in the History? Both the countries although has signed a treaty for extradition and judicial cooperation which is ratified under Federal Law number 38 of 2007 for judicial cooperation between UAE and UK, but has not recognized any bilateral treaty for reciprocal recognition of judgments issued by either country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enjoy Watching Football Tournaments Online in this Pandemic</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/enjoy-watching-football-tournaments-online-in-this-pandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/enjoy-watching-football-tournaments-online-in-this-pandemic/</guid>
      <description>Enjoy Watching Football Tournaments Online in this Pandemic By Amy Burns Published on May 27, 2022   Football is one of the most famous and most followed games worldwide. It is also one of the easiest sports to play. One just needs a fluffy ball and a net only to enjoy the charms of football. But since people now have become busier, they cannot play football due to time constraints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIFA backs the Champions League amidst talks of a rebel European &#39;Super League</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/fifa-backs-the-champions-league-amidst-talks-of-a-rebel-european-super-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/fifa-backs-the-champions-league-amidst-talks-of-a-rebel-european-super-league/</guid>
      <description>FIFA backs the Champions League amidst talks of a rebel European &amp;#39;Super League&amp;#39; By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   The talks of a major breakaway European Super League in place of the Champions League has been on the table for a couple of years and this news came back into prominence last year when the news of banking giant JP Morgan supposedly bankrolling it broke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fight Against Drug Trafficking by GGL</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/fight-against-drug-trafficking-by-ggl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/fight-against-drug-trafficking-by-ggl/</guid>
      <description>Fight Against Drug Trafficking by GGL By Joseph Ballard Published on May 27, 2022   Genaro GarcíaLuna has given phenomenal contribution in the field of international security and intelligence.
As a security consultant, he has worked to serve various Foreign Governments, Security Forces and Intelligence Agencies with exemplary work in drug trafficking and other prominent areas of national interest. His career graph outlines his specialization in serving the security and intelligence agencies with his self-less attitude and dynamism in fulfilling the responsibilities bestowed upon him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Significant Advantages of Microsoft Power BI for Data Scientists</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/five-significant-advantages-of-microsoft-power-bi-for-data-scientists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/five-significant-advantages-of-microsoft-power-bi-for-data-scientists/</guid>
      <description>Five Significant Advantages of Microsoft Power BI for Data Scientists By Jason Adam Katzenstein Published on May 27, 2022   Why Are Companies Choosing BI Solutions?  Businesses in a variety of industries use specialised tools like Power BI for a variety of reasons. They can easily detect upcoming market trends by using these tools. Businesses can assess the viability of their strategies by leveraging Power BI&amp;rsquo;s powerful data analytical capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthy Recipes With Oats And Oatmeal</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/healthy-recipes-with-oats-and-oatmeal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/healthy-recipes-with-oats-and-oatmeal/</guid>
      <description>Healthy Recipes With Oats And Oatmeal By Helen G. Williams Published on May 27, 2022   Oats! What comes into your mind after you hear this word? White mushy food in a very tiny bowl observing you innocently, yearning for your attention. You would possibly be fond of it or not – this tiny bowl has huge potential to keep your health in restraint. Let’s have a glance at some oatmeal recipes to create your meals healthy and attractive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Assignment Help Can Fetch Students from the Dilemma</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-assignment-help-can-fetch-students-from-the-dilemma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-assignment-help-can-fetch-students-from-the-dilemma/</guid>
      <description>How Assignment Help Can Fetch Students from the Dilemma By Helen G. Williams Published on May 27, 2022   Professors assign assignment topics with specific word limits. Students primarily think that they can accomplish this task on their own, but later, when they fail to meet the specified word limit, they become confused about how to fill in the text gap. Writing irrational content is of no use, so they look for a bonafide assignment help so that the content is relevant and meets the expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How climate change plays with the Australian economy</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-climate-change-plays-with-the-australian-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-climate-change-plays-with-the-australian-economy/</guid>
      <description>How climate change plays with the Australian economy By Jason Adam Katzenstein Published on May 27, 2022   Recently, Australia’s financial regulators announced that there’s a need to take serious actions against climate change. The Reserve Bank of Australia, the Australian Prudential Regulation Authority and the Australian Securities and Investment Commission cited the risks posed by climate change on the Australian economy.
How does climate change affect the Australian economy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Perfectly Does Zolpidem Deal With Insomnia?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-perfectly-does-zolpidem-deal-with-insomnia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-perfectly-does-zolpidem-deal-with-insomnia/</guid>
      <description>How Perfectly Does Zolpidem Deal With Insomnia? By Joseph Ballard Published on May 27, 2022   Zolpidem tablets assists to improve your sleep by boosting a chemical in your brain called gamma-aminobutyric acid (GABA). And, these GABA blocks some of the neurotransmitters that send messages in the brain. This includes a calming effect on the brain, which assists you to get to sleep. And, these Zolpidem come as tablets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Studying BTech Data Science Assures a better Future?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-studying-b-tech-data-science-assures-a-better-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-studying-b-tech-data-science-assures-a-better-future/</guid>
      <description>How Studying BTech Data Science Assures a better Future? By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   The programme encompasses data Science as an interdisciplinary, problem-solving oriented subject that learns to apply scientific techniques to practical problems.
Data Science is an exponentially growing field that involves a blend of data inference, algorithm development, and technology to analytically solve complex problems. Some of the Universities conduct BTech Data Science whereas some conducts BTech in Computer Science with specialisation in Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Be More Confident in Public</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-to-be-more-confident-in-public/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-to-be-more-confident-in-public/</guid>
      <description>How to Be More Confident in Public By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   Why are certain things out of your comfort zone? What’s holding you back? After all, there’s a reason you always need a wingman (or woman) with you when you go to parties, or why you’ll never try parasailing on vacation, even though you know you’d have fun.
Now, imagine your life in which you feel confident enough to try a new sport, or take the riskier business deal, or ask for the raise you know you deserve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Break a Negative Habit One Day at a Time</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-to-break-a-negative-habit-one-day-at-a-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-to-break-a-negative-habit-one-day-at-a-time/</guid>
      <description>How to Break a Negative Habit One Day at a Time By Helen G. Williams Published on May 27, 2022   Typically, the top bad habits we indulge in are eating unhealthy foods, smoking, using chewing tobacco, lying on the sofa instead of exercising, and nail-biting.
The good news is, however, that whatever negative habit you have, you have the power to change it if you want to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Buy Affordable Uniforms Online</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-to-buy-affordable-uniforms-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-to-buy-affordable-uniforms-online/</guid>
      <description>How to Buy Affordable Uniforms Online By Liam Cunningham Published on May 27, 2022   This type of uniform also promotes team unity. Baseball jersey outfit and uniforms are made of high-quality fabrics. You can buy them online or from a local sporting goods store.
Baseball uniforms are made of high-quality fabrics To keep your baseball uniforms looking great, you should know how to clean them. The first step in cleaning baseball uniforms is pre-soaking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to choose the best chewy food for your dog?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-to-choose-the-best-chewy-food-for-your-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-to-choose-the-best-chewy-food-for-your-dog/</guid>
      <description>How to choose the best chewy food for your dog? By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   Every pet owner wants to offer the best food, and healthy diet for their four-footed loved dog. A high-quality dog food includes meeting the nutritional standards that are set by AAFCO (Association of American Feed control officials).
High-Quality Dog Food should Contain the following Nutritional Ingredients
Protein that helps in building or repairing tissues, offering energy, helps to promote growth and transport nutrients Fatty acids that help in maintaining healthy skin Amino acids that strengthen the immune system Vitamins and minerals that met your dog’s nutritional requirements</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO DEAL WITH ACNE AND PIGMENTATION FOR DRY SKIN</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-to-deal-with-acne-and-pigmentation-for-dry-skin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-to-deal-with-acne-and-pigmentation-for-dry-skin/</guid>
      <description>HOW TO DEAL WITH ACNE AND PIGMENTATION FOR DRY SKIN By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   Acne and pigmentation are welcomed by none. And for those with Dry skin, dealing with this could be no less than an unpleasant dream.
Dry skin is the most sensitive of all skin types. This makes it more prone to rashes, acne, dark spots and pigmentation. Exposure to UV rays and free radical damage results in skin irritation as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Optimize MySQL Database Performance</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-to-optimize-my-sql-database-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-to-optimize-my-sql-database-performance/</guid>
      <description>How to Optimize MySQL Database Performance By Jason Adam Katzenstein Published on May 27, 2022   An open-source database application that is quite popular and helps store structured data in an accessible and valuable manner is known as MySQL. However, problems in performance with large data applications may appear. That’s why optimization of MySQL database is important.
Balancing the hardware resources MySQL performance tune can be optimized by balancing the hardware resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Teach Yourself a Second Language</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-to-teach-yourself-a-second-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/how-to-teach-yourself-a-second-language/</guid>
      <description>How to Teach Yourself a Second Language By Helen G. Williams Published on May 27, 2022   Studies indicate that learning a second language can improve your memory, brain function, and concentration and open more opportunities. Learning a foreign language is not hard, and anyone with a strong desire can learn a second language fast. If you are a total beginner and looking for ways to teach yourself a foreign language, you’ve come to the right place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jake Paul vs Tyron Woodley Fight Set for Aug. 29 in Cleveland</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/jake-paul-vs-tyron-woodley-fight-set-for-aug-29-in-cleveland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/jake-paul-vs-tyron-woodley-fight-set-for-aug-29-in-cleveland/</guid>
      <description>Jake Paul vs Tyron Woodley Fight Set for Aug. 29 in Cleveland By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   Tyron Woodley&amp;rsquo;s boxing debut versus Jake Paul has a venue.
Jake Paul vs Tyron Woodley Live Stream will headline a Showtime Boxing pay-per-view event on Sunday, Aug. 29, at Rocket Mortgage FieldHouse in Cleveland, Showtime announced Monday. Paul grew up in Cleveland.
“I grew up attending to Cavs, Browns, and Indians games on weekends, fantasizing as a young child of one day being in a position to put on a show for my city like they did,” Paul stated in a press release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karma Doesn&#39;t Work How Most People Think It Does</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/karma-doesn-t-work-how-most-people-think-it-does/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/karma-doesn-t-work-how-most-people-think-it-does/</guid>
      <description>Karma Doesn&amp;#39;t Work How Most People Think It Does By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   Eastern traditions have a complex view on how karma affects our life; it views it as a part of a cycle of birth and rebirth. Our actions and intentions can influence karma, which can be both positive and negative.
The news of Donald Trump getting sick with Covid-19 caused the word ‘karma’ to trend on social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest Trends in IT and Its Impact on Outsourcing</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/latest-trends-in-it-and-its-impact-on-outsourcing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/latest-trends-in-it-and-its-impact-on-outsourcing/</guid>
      <description>Latest Trends in IT and Its Impact on Outsourcing By Margaret F. Wise Published on May 27, 2022   With the competition in the IT sector constantly on the rise, companies are becoming increasingly reliant on outsourced services. By 2026, IT outsourcing is likely to have a market volume of around USD 552 billion. The yearly growth rate (CAGR 2021 to 2026) from 2021 onwards is projected to be around 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lifestyles</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/topic/lifestyles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/topic/lifestyles/</guid>
      <description>Lifestyles Describes an individual&amp;#39;s attitude, way of life, values, or worldview.    8 Tips to Motivate Your Lazy Self  Helen G. Williams • May 27, 2022   How to choose the best chewy food for your dog?  Ying Leak • May 27, 2022   How Perfectly Does Zolpidem Deal With Insomnia?  Joseph Ballard • May 27, 2022   HOW TO DEAL WITH ACNE AND PIGMENTATION FOR DRY SKIN  Ying Leak • May 27, 2022   Karma Doesn&amp;#39;t Work How Most People Think It Does  Ying Leak • May 27, 2022   Most Important Beauty Tips Every Woman Must Know  Helen G.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maldini - a quarter of a century of credibility</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/maldini-a-quarter-of-a-century-of-credibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/maldini-a-quarter-of-a-century-of-credibility/</guid>
      <description>Maldini - a quarter of a century of credibility By Liam Cunningham Published on May 27, 2022   When Paolo Maldini broke the original lineup of AC Milan in the fall of 1985, an estimated 4.8 billion people called the planet Earth home. By the end of his defence career, he had two billion more neighbours.
  5x Champions League winner (1988/89, 1989/90, 1993/94, 2002/03, 2006/07)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Important Beauty Tips Every Woman Must Know</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/most-important-beauty-tips-every-woman-must-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/most-important-beauty-tips-every-woman-must-know/</guid>
      <description>Most Important Beauty Tips Every Woman Must Know By Helen G. Williams Published on May 27, 2022   As the connective materials (fibroblast) come into the hurt region, they start mending the spot by creating bovine collagen. Often acne (bad acne scar laser) surgical marks result in the cutis concave or chorus behindhand, an impossible red-colored business owner that will not diminish. This bad acne scar procedure needs to be specifically completed by a dermatologic cosmetic surgeon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Buying Trends Emerge for Shoppers</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/new-buying-trends-emerge-for-shoppers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/new-buying-trends-emerge-for-shoppers/</guid>
      <description>New Buying Trends Emerge for Shoppers By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   When the economy nosedived, and companies had reason to be scared, a few businesses got resourceful. Low incomes and record job losses pushed consumers toward trends like buying in bulk and using group discount websites. And where there was demand, supply soon followed.
In came the success of wholesalers like Costco, Sam’s Club and BJ’s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/topic/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/topic/news/</guid>
      <description>News Contemporary announcements from around the world.    Top 15 Companies Giving Best White Label NFT Marketplace Services  Joseph Ballard • May 27, 2022   Brazil Invest in New Transport Monitoring System  Ying Leak • May 27, 2022   Fight Against Drug Trafficking by GGL  Joseph Ballard • May 27, 2022   How climate change plays with the Australian economy  Jason Adam Katzenstein • May 27, 2022   US-China fight over Covid 19  Ying Leak • May 27, 2022   Travel updates in the UAE: Your Legal Guide during Pandemic  Jason Adam Katzenstein • May 27, 2022   Discovering Florida Arrest Records Public Search  Joseph Ballard • May 27, 2022   Are You Fired Illegally: Get You Right Back with Wrongful Termination Lawyers  Joseph Ballard • May 27, 2022   What are the Punishments for Physical Assault In Public?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Learning Platform – A Levels &amp; More</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/online-learning-platform-a-levels-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/online-learning-platform-a-levels-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Online Learning Platform – A Levels &amp;amp; More By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   A-Levels Online Learning Every country usually has its own education system, but the UK-based A-Levels is a qualification course used and accepted worldwide! Any student with the age of 16 or above can participate in this subject-based course which spans over a period of 2 years; A Levels online being the preferred option for many learners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parent&#39;s Checklist: Factors to Keep in Mind When Selecting a Youth Football Academy</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/parent-s-checklist-factors-to-keep-in-mind-when-selecting-a-youth-football-academy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/parent-s-checklist-factors-to-keep-in-mind-when-selecting-a-youth-football-academy/</guid>
      <description>Parent&amp;#39;s Checklist: Factors to Keep in Mind When Selecting a Youth Football Academy By Amy Burns Published on May 27, 2022   With hundreds of academies out there, choosing the one for football coaching specializing in American football tournaments won&amp;rsquo;t be easy. Several factors need to be considered before thinking of signing up your kid for an academy; after all, your child&amp;rsquo;s future depends on the academy you will pick for them today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Still Optimistic Despite Big Swings in The Market</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/people-still-optimistic-despite-big-swings-in-the-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/people-still-optimistic-despite-big-swings-in-the-market/</guid>
      <description>People Still Optimistic Despite Big Swings in The Market By Jason Adam Katzenstein Published on May 27, 2022   Even though the stock market continues to engage in wild swings, people are still predicting a better year financially.
That sense of optimism was one of the most striking findings in Fidelity Investments’ tenth annual “New Year Financial Resolutions Study,” and could be an encouraging sign that – despite December’s rockiest performance in decades by all the major U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerPoint Free Course - Tips and Tricks for Business Presentations</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/power-point-free-course-tips-and-tricks-for-business-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/power-point-free-course-tips-and-tricks-for-business-presentations/</guid>
      <description>PowerPoint Free Course - Tips and Tricks for Business Presentations By Helen G. Williams Published on May 27, 2022   PowerPoint is one application that helps many people in their day-to-day work. Starting from school students making their school projects to sales associates and business people who make their daily reports too.
There are many tips and tricks that people in business should learn to give outstanding presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Premier League circuit break: Will football be halted for two weeks?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/premier-league-circuit-break-will-football-be-halted-for-two-weeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/premier-league-circuit-break-will-football-be-halted-for-two-weeks/</guid>
      <description>Premier League circuit break: Will football be halted for two weeks? By Liam Cunningham Published on May 27, 2022   A new variant of the coronavirus has emerged in the United Kingdom causing a sharp rise in positive cases amongst the Premier League clubs.
Manchester City&amp;rsquo;s game vs Everton on Monday had to be postponed due to some City players and staff testing positive and in the latest round of testing, 18 people have turned out to be positive - the highest figure so far this season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick and Easy Packing Tips for a Barge Holiday in France</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/quick-and-easy-packing-tips-for-a-barge-holiday-in-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/quick-and-easy-packing-tips-for-a-barge-holiday-in-france/</guid>
      <description>Quick and Easy Packing Tips for a Barge Holiday in France By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   If you’ve made the very exciting decision to embark on a barge holiday in France, you’ve no doubt spent many hours thinking about all that time you’ll have to relax, see the countryside and enjoy spectacular food and wine alongside likeminded people. However, if this is your first time experiencing this wonderful way to explore a country (or even if you just haven’t been for a long time) it can be very helpful to know what to pack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Requirements for the Main Applicant Tracking System</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/requirements-for-the-main-applicant-tracking-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/requirements-for-the-main-applicant-tracking-system/</guid>
      <description>Requirements for the Main Applicant Tracking System By Kerry Elson Published on May 27, 2022   As a small business owner, you do not always have the luxury of installing software that partners can use to improve their processes. You learn so quickly that you have to do a little more to stay ahead of the competition. For this reason, you should choose and decide what costs you will invest in because every time is important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rockin’ to the Beat: Tips for Enjoying a Live Concert</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/rockin-to-the-beat-tips-for-enjoying-a-live-concert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/rockin-to-the-beat-tips-for-enjoying-a-live-concert/</guid>
      <description>Rockin’ to the Beat: Tips for Enjoying a Live Concert By Joseph Ballard Published on May 27, 2022   A concert is more than an event, it’s an experience. This is a chance to get dressed up, go out on the town, connect with your friends and maybe just discover a hot new band that you want to add to your playlist.
For some, however, the pressure may be too much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selenium VS Tosca - Automation Testing Tools</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/selenium-vs-tosca-automation-testing-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/selenium-vs-tosca-automation-testing-tools/</guid>
      <description>Selenium VS Tosca - Automation Testing Tools By Margaret F. Wise Published on May 27, 2022   What is Selenium? Selenium is a popular open-source tool for automating web application testing. Selenium can be used to automate the testing of web applications in multiple browsers, operating systems, and devices. Selenium supports a wide range of programming languages, making it an ideal choice for test automation for Selenium testers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Home Security Systems</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/smart-home-security-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/smart-home-security-systems/</guid>
      <description>Smart Home Security Systems By Jason Adam Katzenstein Published on May 27, 2022   US is effectively witnessing rapid digital transformation all over a wide range of fields, and market sentiment suggests that this transformation may only be the starting of what’s to come.
The whole tech transformation has created an entirely new segment that is presently the main topic of conversation in India, Smart Homes, which is estimated to rise to more than $14 billion by 2026.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sports</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/topic/sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/topic/sports/</guid>
      <description>Sports Form of writing that reports on matters pertaining to sporting topics.    Ten Most Amazing Stadiums Around The World Which Every Sports Lover Should Know  Liam Cunningham • May 27, 2022   Buy Genuine Premier League Football Tickets At Competitive Rates  James Anthony Knight • May 27, 2022   Enjoy Watching Football Tournaments Online in this Pandemic  Amy Burns • May 27, 2022   Maldini - a quarter of a century of credibility  Liam Cunningham • May 27, 2022   Cannabis In Sports  Amy Burns • May 27, 2022   Premier League circuit break: Will football be halted for two weeks?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Become a Mixologist</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/steps-to-become-a-mixologist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/steps-to-become-a-mixologist/</guid>
      <description>Steps to Become a Mixologist By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   Enrolling in a hotel or hospitality management course is a great career path and opens up a plethora of avenues for you but what it lacks is specialization; something which is becoming exceedingly important in today’s day and age. This is why there exist courses which train you in a specific skill and is a sure shot way of landing a job in that field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study Shows Older Americans Are Coping Best During the Pandemic</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/study-shows-older-americans-are-coping-best-during-the-pandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/study-shows-older-americans-are-coping-best-during-the-pandemic/</guid>
      <description>Study Shows Older Americans Are Coping Best During the Pandemic By Joseph Ballard Published on May 27, 2022   If you think older Americans have struggled to cope through the pandemic, think again. According to new research by financial services firm Edward Jones, they have actually been faring far better than their younger counterparts.
The Edward Jones and Age Wave Study focused exclusively on how different generations have held up emotionally and financially in the months since the lockdowns began, and some of its findings are at least as startling as how quickly even 70-year-olds came to love Zoom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teach Yourself to Become a Bookkeeper</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/teach-yourself-to-become-a-bookkeeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/teach-yourself-to-become-a-bookkeeper/</guid>
      <description>Teach Yourself to Become a Bookkeeper By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   This article provides some tips on how to teach yourself how to become a bookkeeper. It will also give you some information on skills needed to succeed in this profession.
Roles of a Bookkeeper To become a bookkeeper, you’ll first need to understand what a bookkeeper does and the education and skills required to become one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technologies Trend that will Change Transportation Industry Forever!</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/technologies-trend-that-will-change-transportation-industry-forever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/technologies-trend-that-will-change-transportation-industry-forever/</guid>
      <description>Technologies Trend that will Change Transportation Industry Forever! By Margaret F. Wise Published on May 27, 2022   Transportation technology is undergoing a revolution. Emerging technologies are increasing the performance of conventional modes of transportation, while new inventions are positioned to completely revolutionize the way we progress. The transportation industry, like every other industry, is adopting technological trends to improve productivity. However, it is important to note that these technological trends will not only improve productivity but will also transform the transportation industry forever!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technology</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/topic/technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/topic/technology/</guid>
      <description>Technology Be knowledgeable with information about technology.    What is headless CMS development and when do you need it?  Margaret F. Wise • May 27, 2022   Best 5 Android Frameworks for App Development  Jason Adam Katzenstein • May 27, 2022   7 Strong Reasons to Invest in the .NET Framework in 2021  Ali Fitzgerald • May 27, 2022   Top 10 Tips for Android App Development Success  Jason Adam Katzenstein • May 27, 2022   IoT Application Testing - Complexities &amp;amp; Challenges  Jason Adam Katzenstein • May 27, 2022   12 Reasons for React Native App Development Popularity  Kerry Elson • May 27, 2022   How to Optimize MySQL Database Performance  Jason Adam Katzenstein • May 27, 2022   Things To Look For In A LED Screen  Kerry Elson • May 27, 2022   Latest Trends in IT and Its Impact on Outsourcing  Margaret F.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ten Most Amazing Stadiums Around The World Which Every Sports Lover Should Know</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/ten-most-amazing-stadiums-around-the-world-which-every-sports-lover-should-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/ten-most-amazing-stadiums-around-the-world-which-every-sports-lover-should-know/</guid>
      <description>Ten Most Amazing Stadiums Around The World Which Every Sports Lover Should Know By Liam Cunningham Published on May 27, 2022   You cannot find the immensity and the energy that any sports stadiums possess in itself anywhere else. Moreover, every sports stadium has his own stories to tell. The stadium experience every type of emotion at every game. In a nutshell, every day in a stadium is itself a story to tell, and every sports lover should know these stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Advantages of Using Free Online Courses</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/the-advantages-of-using-free-online-courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/the-advantages-of-using-free-online-courses/</guid>
      <description>The Advantages of Using Free Online Courses By Helen G. Williams Published on May 27, 2022   Online learning has grown in popularity in recent years as the quality of the free online courses has grown. Online learning can take whatever form you need it for. It can give a student the chance to complete work from home, fill in missing information, follow an area of interest, or improve your education for your future career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Gear When Going Surfing: Buy Mens Boardshorts Trunks Online</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/the-complete-gear-when-going-surfing-buy-mens-boardshorts-trunks-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/the-complete-gear-when-going-surfing-buy-mens-boardshorts-trunks-online/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Gear When Going Surfing: Buy Mens Boardshorts Trunks Online By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   To surfers, the water and waves could either be your best friend or worst foe. And with such a dangerous sport or hobby, it is only important to always wear complete and proper equipment when going surfing. Buying surfing equipment can be as easy as typing Buy mens boardshorts trunks online, but it might seem confusing as to what are the essential equipment and what the function of each is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Impact of Patient-Tracking Technology on Healthcare</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/the-impact-of-patient-tracking-technology-on-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/the-impact-of-patient-tracking-technology-on-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>The Impact of Patient-Tracking Technology on Healthcare By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   Technology has so much to offer to the healthcare industry. Things like cost-effectiveness, high-quality health services, user-friendly enrollment/appointment sessions, improved patient experience, or satisfaction are there for the taking. Clinicians, medical billing companies, patients, hence, every stakeholder of the healthcare industry owes it to technology, innovation, and research conducted in this sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Most Popular Sports In The World</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/the-most-popular-sports-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/the-most-popular-sports-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>The Most Popular Sports In The World By Amy Burns Published on May 27, 2022   Sport is a culture that can bring people together, irrespective of differences in culture, religion, or values. It is a culture that is old as time. Sport has encountered immense transition as time changes. Sport can involve two people, or a group of people comes together to make the team. A team is like a machine with different parts but with the same goal and mission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things To Look For In A LED Screen</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/things-to-look-for-in-a-led-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/things-to-look-for-in-a-led-screen/</guid>
      <description>Things To Look For In A LED Screen By Kerry Elson Published on May 27, 2022   Most of us need a LED screen, and hence it becomes essential to find a supplier who gets the best indoor LED screen for your requirements. But at the same time, because the investment is a bit hefty, it is essential to have the basics in mind and narrow down your search.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Modern Woodwind Classics That&#39;ll Take Your Breath Away</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/three-modern-woodwind-classics-that-ll-take-your-breath-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/three-modern-woodwind-classics-that-ll-take-your-breath-away/</guid>
      <description>Three Modern Woodwind Classics That&amp;#39;ll Take Your Breath Away By Helen G. Williams Published on May 27, 2022   Woodwind instruments have some of the most intense depths of sound and tone of any type of instrument. There is a certain, haunting soul that you can capture on a saxophone or clarinet that is more di?cult to get on a piano. Despite this, woodwinds are criminally underused in many types of music, and very often, are confined to ‘traditional’ classical music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Reasons Why Sports Mediation Is Better Than Sports Arbitration</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/three-reasons-why-sports-mediation-is-better-than-sports-arbitration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/three-reasons-why-sports-mediation-is-better-than-sports-arbitration/</guid>
      <description>Three Reasons Why Sports Mediation Is Better Than Sports Arbitration By Liam Cunningham Published on May 27, 2022   The habits of people have changed considerably at sporting events. You find many people that primarily do not look at their surroundings at all. They seem to be looking at their smartphones and electronic devices as if someone is talking to them already. Other than this, some people cannot take their eyes off mobiles because they read emails or watch videos or play games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Ways Millennials Can Start Saving More Money</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/three-ways-millennials-can-start-saving-more-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/three-ways-millennials-can-start-saving-more-money/</guid>
      <description>Three Ways Millennials Can Start Saving More Money By Helen G. Williams Published on May 27, 2022   For too long, Millennials have gotten a bad rap about money and their ability to save for a rainy day or retirement.
However, a new “Relationship With Money” survey by financial services firm Edward Jones found that not only do more Americans born between 1981 and 1996 consider themselves “savers” than those in their parents’ Gen-X cohort (48 percent vs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ticket Packages Launched for 2022 World Juniors</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/ticket-packages-launched-for-2022-world-juniors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/ticket-packages-launched-for-2022-world-juniors/</guid>
      <description>Ticket Packages Launched for 2022 World Juniors By Amy Burns Published on May 27, 2022   In the 2022 IIHF World Junior Championship set to start with games in Edmonton as well as Red Deer, Alta. This month, Hockey Canada has announced three ticket packages for fans who can buy to guarantee their spot for the annual holiday hockey event.
&amp;ldquo;There is a tremendous amount of anticipation for the World Juniors Live Stream to return to Edmonton and Red Deer after last year&amp;rsquo;s event without fans, and we are excited to launch three great ticket packages and allow fans to secure their seats to see the top under-20 players in the world,&amp;rdquo; said Riley Wiwchar, executive director of the 2022 IIHF World Junior Championship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips for choosing the best mens surf board shorts for you</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/tips-for-choosing-the-best-mens-surf-board-shorts-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/tips-for-choosing-the-best-mens-surf-board-shorts-for-you/</guid>
      <description>Tips for choosing the best mens surf board shorts for you By Liam Cunningham Published on May 27, 2022   Where do you even start your search when you’re looking for mens surfing t shirts or surf board shorts?
**These tips will help to make your search easier. **
Choose the right material While canvas and cotton shorts look good and fall really well, these are not suitable for wearing in the water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips to get your healthy lifestyle start</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/tips-to-get-your-healthy-lifestyle-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/tips-to-get-your-healthy-lifestyle-start/</guid>
      <description>Tips to get your healthy lifestyle start By Joseph Ballard Published on May 27, 2022   A healthy lifestyle is a key to enjoyment. It is correct to conclude that if you are healthier, you will automatically remain happy. However, it is important for us to recognize the ways that will make you healthy. Maintaining a healthy lifestyle is not a very difficult task, you can easily follow it using some simple techniques such as bringing changes in your diet, consuming a lesser amount of salt and sugar, reducing the intake of harmful fats, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Tips for Android App Development Success</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/top-10-tips-for-android-app-development-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/top-10-tips-for-android-app-development-success/</guid>
      <description>Top 10 Tips for Android App Development Success By Jason Adam Katzenstein Published on May 27, 2022   As of now, there are over 3.1 million apps accessible in the Google Play Store, and that number is just going up. Obviously, it&amp;rsquo;s an incredible time to get familiar with some best Android development tips from the strong Android developers worldwide.
Since its first commercial delivery came in 2008, the little robot has ended up being the dearest companion to end-users and its developers at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 15 Companies Giving Best White Label NFT Marketplace Services</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/top-15-companies-giving-best-white-label-nft-marketplace-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/top-15-companies-giving-best-white-label-nft-marketplace-services/</guid>
      <description>Top 15 Companies Giving Best White Label NFT Marketplace Services By Joseph Ballard Published on May 27, 2022   NFTs have gotten a lot of attention over the last few years. After the rise of blockchain technology, this trend arose.
Blockchain has attracted a lot of interest. Recognizing the value of this technology, various businesses and industries are using it to safeguard their data and transactions. The success of the NFTs was not achieved overnight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 6 NFT Marketplace Clone Scripts That Makes Your Business More Profitable</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/top-6-nft-marketplace-clone-scripts-that-makes-your-business-more-profitable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/top-6-nft-marketplace-clone-scripts-that-makes-your-business-more-profitable/</guid>
      <description>Top 6 NFT Marketplace Clone Scripts That Makes Your Business More Profitable By Joseph Ballard Published on May 27, 2022   In this generation, most peoples are highly influenced by the latest technologies, especially Blockchain. Non-Fungible Token (NFT) Marketplace is one of the buzz work in the technology world. From the fact that Crypto-collectibles is one of the gaining assets in the digital world, many crypto investors are started to invest on the NFT platforms instead of cryptocurrencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Football Betting Tips that You Should Know!</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/top-football-betting-tips-that-you-should-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/top-football-betting-tips-that-you-should-know/</guid>
      <description>Top Football Betting Tips that You Should Know! By Liam Cunningham Published on May 27, 2022   Millions of people place bets on football every day. It is a famous sports worldwide to play and place bets on. With the Football world cup 2022 around the corner, the craze for football betting is again at its peak.
Because of the popularity of football, it is so easy to find information related to the sports that will assist you in placing bets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top IoT trends to check for in 2022</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/top-io-t-trends-to-check-for-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/top-io-t-trends-to-check-for-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>Top IoT trends to check for in 2022 By Ali Fitzgerald Published on May 27, 2022   IoT has been gaining popularity across the world and it doesn’t seem like this is about to change any time soon. From corporate applications to personal and household electronics, IoT has been making its way into every sphere. Although the popularity of IoT was already gaining momentum for a while, the pandemic situation was a big catalyst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Online MBA Programs in New York</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/top-online-mba-programs-in-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/top-online-mba-programs-in-new-york/</guid>
      <description>Top Online MBA Programs in New York By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   There are a number of top rated online MBA (Master of Business Administration) program schools in the state of New York, including Hofstra University, Clarkson University, Syracuse University, and Marist College.
Hofstra University’s Online MBA Program is the first distance learning program in strategic business management in New York. It was ranked 71st nationwide and was the only online graduate business program in the New York metropolitan area to make the top 100, according to U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Remote Patient Monitoring Companies in Virginia</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/top-remote-patient-monitoring-companies-in-virginia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/top-remote-patient-monitoring-companies-in-virginia/</guid>
      <description>Top Remote Patient Monitoring Companies in Virginia By Kerry Elson Published on May 27, 2022   Healthcare systems in the United States are encouraging practitioners to use a new type of healthcare facility in their diagnosing process, according to government norms and rules. A remote patient monitoring program is what it&amp;rsquo;s called. This healthcare facility allows patients to communicate directly with doctors without having to physically visit the clinic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel updates in the UAE: Your Legal Guide during Pandemic</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/travel-updates-in-the-uae-your-legal-guide-during-pandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/travel-updates-in-the-uae-your-legal-guide-during-pandemic/</guid>
      <description>Travel updates in the UAE: Your Legal Guide during Pandemic By Jason Adam Katzenstein Published on May 27, 2022   The UAE currently leads the world nations in the number of Covid-19 vaccines administered, with 93% of its population being vaccinated and 82 % being fully vaccinated. This is a staggering achievement and combined with the Covid-19 protection measures, the country has successfully brought life close to normal, with residents being able to enjoy a freer and healthy environment in comparison with other nations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelling Solo? Consider a River Cruise in Italy!</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/travelling-solo-consider-a-river-cruise-in-italy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/travelling-solo-consider-a-river-cruise-in-italy/</guid>
      <description>Travelling Solo? Consider a River Cruise in Italy! By Helen G. Williams Published on May 27, 2022   If you’re looking to discover the authentic heart of Europe away from the thronging crowds of the cities, why not consider a cruise along some of the continent’s historic waterways? With networks of canals crisscrossing through scenic countryside, picturesque towns and even cities, a river cruise in Italy is one of the best ways to experience a unique perspective of the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the importance and benefits of Argan Oil for the Face</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/understanding-the-importance-and-benefits-of-argan-oil-for-the-face/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/understanding-the-importance-and-benefits-of-argan-oil-for-the-face/</guid>
      <description>Understanding the importance and benefits of Argan Oil for the Face By Helen G. Williams Published on May 27, 2022   Argan oil comes from the kernels of dried Argan fruit produced by the Argan trees that are native to the desert region of Morocco. The local Berber people have traditionally used this oil for culinary, medicinal, and cosmetic purposes. In its purest form, the suitability of Argan oil for the face, hair, and nails applications is well-proven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US-China fight over Covid 19</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/us-china-fight-over-covid-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/us-china-fight-over-covid-19/</guid>
      <description>US-China fight over Covid 19 By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   The Trump administration and the Chinese government are going head to head over the Coronavirus. Xi Jinping and Donald Trump have an incentive to point the finger at the other guy at the other country and say, look, they&amp;rsquo;re the ones to blame for all of our trouble. Number one, we don&amp;rsquo;t know what the numbers are in China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Are The Future Career Choices For Economics Students?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-are-the-future-career-choices-for-economics-students/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-are-the-future-career-choices-for-economics-students/</guid>
      <description>What Are The Future Career Choices For Economics Students? By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   Economics is a discipline focused on understanding the human behaviour and using it to shape the world around us. It is one of the evergreen subjects because of its high utility and huge demand in the job markets. It is also an important multidisciplinary subject both from a career and job perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are the general commercial liability policies in the UAE?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-are-the-general-commercial-liability-policies-in-the-uae/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-are-the-general-commercial-liability-policies-in-the-uae/</guid>
      <description>What are the general commercial liability policies in the UAE? By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   A CGL policy thus endeavors to cover the various liabilities arising from operations, premises, products of a business under one policy. The broadheads covered under a commercial liability policy in the UAE includes:
  Property Damage: A CGL policy will cover the instances wherein property damage is caused to another person or company on account of your business operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are the Punishments for Physical Assault In Public?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-are-the-punishments-for-physical-assault-in-public/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-are-the-punishments-for-physical-assault-in-public/</guid>
      <description>What are the Punishments for Physical Assault In Public? By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   Different categories of assault and their punishments:
The Federal law no. 3 of 1987 concerning promulgating the penal code and its amendment (UAE Penal Code), categories ‘assault’ into various types, such as:
 Assault causing death  A person shall be sentenced to imprisonment for a period not exceeding ten years, whoever assaults the body safety of others, by any means without intention to kill him but the assault resulted in the death of the victim (Article 336).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Are The Top Software Testing Trends In 2022?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-are-the-top-software-testing-trends-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-are-the-top-software-testing-trends-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>What Are The Top Software Testing Trends In 2022? By Margaret F. Wise Published on May 27, 2022   The dynamic evolution of technology is affecting an organization in the following terms development, validations, usage, operations, etc. Thus, these organizations are in constant need of innovation and transformation with solutions that optimize regular practices to deliver high-quality software quickly.
Software testing mainly focuses on changes and improvements. It is most important to achieve quality software at speed despite the increase in the complexity of systems, environments, and data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Differs Power BI From Other BI Tools?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-differs-power-bi-from-other-bi-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-differs-power-bi-from-other-bi-tools/</guid>
      <description>What Differs Power BI From Other BI Tools? By Jason Adam Katzenstein Published on May 27, 2022   WHAT MAKES POWER BI UNIQUE?
Power BI has many features, including a data modeling tool with a user-friendly interface and a multi-layered business solution. Any BI tool is made up of three parts:
 Raw Data: The data acquired from the data source is presented in an unstructured format. Reports: Reports are the output of any BI tool that displays the data in a graphical way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is headless CMS development and when do you need it?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-is-headless-cms-development-and-when-do-you-need-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-is-headless-cms-development-and-when-do-you-need-it/</guid>
      <description>What is headless CMS development and when do you need it? By Margaret F. Wise Published on May 27, 2022   For that reason, more and more businesses employ different digital products to promote themselves. It includes social media networking, digital platforms, and web applications. However, with such a big range of components, it can be hard to manage them all at once to achieve consistency. Hopefully, there are several ways, and one of the most efficient ones is the use of headless CMS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is the full list of fines for money laundering in the UAE? Dr. Hassan Elhais</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-is-the-full-list-of-fines-for-money-laundering-in-the-uae-dr-hassan-elhais/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-is-the-full-list-of-fines-for-money-laundering-in-the-uae-dr-hassan-elhais/</guid>
      <description>What is the full list of fines for money laundering in the UAE? Dr. Hassan Elhais By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   Around twenty-six categories of fines have been listed, ranging from AED 50,000 to AED 1,000,000.
In addition to step up the monitoring of money laundering activities in the UAE, the ministry has established a specialized administrative unit .The said unit is authorized for the inspection and control of designated non-financial businesses and professions such as real estate agents and brokers, dealers of precious metals and gemstones, auditors, corporate service providers etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is UFC president Dana White’s net worth?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-is-ufc-president-dana-white-s-net-worth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-is-ufc-president-dana-white-s-net-worth/</guid>
      <description>What is UFC president Dana White’s net worth? By Amy Burns Published on May 27, 2022   According to gossipop.com, White&amp;rsquo;s projected net worth is over $500 million ahead of UFC 264, which features a trilogy fight between Dustin Poirier and Conor McGregor. But does it stop there? The simple answer is no, since White&amp;rsquo;s hobbies span from expensive automobiles to excessive rounds of blackjack at Las Vegas casinos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What should you rinse with after a tooth extraction?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-should-you-rinse-with-after-a-tooth-extraction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-should-you-rinse-with-after-a-tooth-extraction/</guid>
      <description>What should you rinse with after a tooth extraction? By Helen G. Williams Published on May 27, 2022   After a tooth extraction, there are specific instructions about what you can and cannot do. You need to follow them very closely to avoid continuous bleeding from the extraction socket.
Post-Operative instructions for an extraction:
 On the day of the procedure - do not rinse, do not spit, and no drinking through a straw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What will be the punishment for fake claims in court?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-will-be-the-punishment-for-fake-claims-in-court/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-will-be-the-punishment-for-fake-claims-in-court/</guid>
      <description>What will be the punishment for fake claims in court? By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   In this article, we will endeavour to discuss the concept of making fake claims or accusations under UAE law and it’s resultant punishments. The federal law no. 3 of 1987 and its amendments (the UAE Civil Code) defines the act of providing false reports to judicial or administrative authorities in the UAE as a punishable offence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What You Need to Know About Hearsay Evidence in Australia</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-you-need-to-know-about-hearsay-evidence-in-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/what-you-need-to-know-about-hearsay-evidence-in-australia/</guid>
      <description>What You Need to Know About Hearsay Evidence in Australia By Joseph Ballard Published on May 27, 2022   The hearsay rule is contained in section 59 of the evidence act 1995. It states, “Evidence of a previous representation made by a person is not admissible to prove the existence of a fact that it can reasonably be supposed that the person intended to assert by the representation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Can I Find Cheap MLB Baseball Jerseys?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/where-can-i-find-cheap-mlb-baseball-jerseys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/where-can-i-find-cheap-mlb-baseball-jerseys/</guid>
      <description>Where Can I Find Cheap MLB Baseball Jerseys? By Liam Cunningham Published on May 27, 2022   There are a lot of ways to get cheap MLB jerseys without spending a bunch of money. Here are a few of the best ways to find those cheap custom baseball uniforms without spending a lot of money.
One of the easiest ways to get cheap jerseys is to buy them wholesale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which is better, diploma or degree culinary program</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/which-is-better-diploma-or-degree-culinary-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/which-is-better-diploma-or-degree-culinary-program/</guid>
      <description>Which is better, diploma or degree culinary program By Helen G. Williams Published on May 27, 2022   Choosing to pursue a career in the culinary arts is one of the numerous critical decisions you will make for your future. Another major decision is whether you need to pursue a Culinary Certificate/diploma or a Culinary Degree. The answer to that question weighs vigorously on the kind of career you are pursuing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Should I Learn Artificial Intelligence?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/why-should-i-learn-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/why-should-i-learn-artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>Why Should I Learn Artificial Intelligence? By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   Artificial intelligence is essential for the enhancement of the speed, effectiveness, and appreciation of human efforts. When it comes to Financial Institutions to several other industries, artificial intelligence techniques can be used for identification, recording the transactions that usually turn out to be fraudulent. In addition to that, artificial intelligence learning is applicable in the different sectors of the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why should you opt for PGDM instead of MBA?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/why-should-you-opt-for-pgdm-instead-of-mba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/why-should-you-opt-for-pgdm-instead-of-mba/</guid>
      <description>Why should you opt for PGDM instead of MBA? By Ying Leak Published on May 27, 2022   There is no doubt that Masters in Business Administration, commonly known as MBA, is one of the most favorite choices of career aspirants. This is because the boys and girls see innumerable job prospects opening up in front of them after securing MBA. In addition, those who aspire to start their own business expect to gain entrepreneurial skills with the study of MBA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Use Coursera Clone as an Education Script?</title>
      <link>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/why-use-coursera-clone-as-an-education-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://202.56.164.148:5001/article/why-use-coursera-clone-as-an-education-script/</guid>
      <description>Why Use Coursera Clone as an Education Script? By James Anthony Knight Published on May 27, 2022   Who Uses Education Script? The major gatherings of education script customers are teachers, understudies, gatekeepers, and school administrators. Every get-together uses education script to chip away at their educational experience, diminish disappointments, and work with correspondence. A large portion of education script is expected administrators and educators to make content, share works out, regulate center around antechambers, and house school-and understudy related data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
